<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://yingyan-xu.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 23:52:44 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yingyan-xu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ABOUT</title>
      <link>https://yingyan-xu.github.io/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 23:52:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yingyan-xu.github.io/post/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a third year undergraduate student in Department of Automation, Shanghai Jiao Tong University, expecting to graduate in June 2019.
My research interests include video analysis, robotic vision and general problems in computer vision. My current work focuses on dense detailed multi-label action detection tasks in untrimmed videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDUCATION</title>
      <link>https://yingyan-xu.github.io/post/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 00:07:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yingyan-xu.github.io/post/education/</guid>
      <description>SHANGHAI JIAO TONG UNIVERSITY
 Major in Automation, School of Electronic Information and Electrical Engineering Average Score: 90.4 / 100 Rank: 3 / 91
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INTERNSHIP</title>
      <link>https://yingyan-xu.github.io/post/internship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:20:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yingyan-xu.github.io/post/internship/</guid>
      <description>HIKVISION RESEARCH INSTITUTE Research Intern, Intelligent Algorithm Department
I’ve recently been researching on visual analysis of human activity and have done some related work, listed as follows:
 Examined large-scale video benchmark datasets which depict a variety of complex human activities in untrimmed videos, including Charades, THUMOS and MultiTHUMOS.
 Learned the basic ideas of existing approaches on MultiTHUMOS, including MultiLSTM, predictive-corrective networks, biLSTM, siLSTM and super-event presentation. Briefly compared their strengths and weaknesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PROJECTS</title>
      <link>https://yingyan-xu.github.io/post/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 00:24:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yingyan-xu.github.io/post/projects/</guid>
      <description>Obstacle Detection for Vision Based Navigation for Autonomous Driving Autonomous Robot Lab, SJTU
  Detecting the obstacles accurately and reliably is important for navigating the robot or autonomous vehicle. The cost effective monocular camera sensor along with computer vision techniques plays a key role in making this pragmatically realizable. Deep Neural Networks like Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) are widely used for object detection and segmentation algorithms.
 Used the SegNet encoder-decoder architecture for pixel-wise semantic segmentation of the video frame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COURSEWORK</title>
      <link>https://yingyan-xu.github.io/post/coursework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 00:26:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yingyan-xu.github.io/post/coursework/</guid>
      <description> UPCOMING COURSES   AU419 Computer Networking Fall 2018 SJTU   AU422 Operation Systems Fall 2018 SJTU   CS400 Database Fall 2018 SJTU   COMPLETED COURSES   CS430 Data Structure 100 SJTU   CS048 C++ Programing 98 SJTU   CS331 Computer Control Technology  100 SJTU   AU416 Robotics 97 SJTU   AU310 Motion Control Systems 95 SJTU   AU326 Digital Image Processing 90 SJTU   AU311 Pattern Recognition 90 SJTU   EI304 Principles of Automatic Control 92 SJTU   MA119 Probability and Statistics 90 SJTU   MA043 Mathematical Analysis 93 SJTU   MA115 Discrete Mathematics 88 SJTU   MA077 Linear Algebra 87 SJTU   AU302 Modern Control Theory 98 SJTU   AU308 Digital Signal Processing 97 SJTU   EE213 Embedded Systems 98 SJTU   PH002 Physics 97 SJTU   ONLINE COURSES   Deep Learning Summer 2018 Coursera   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>